export const lvl9 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What industry is the largest employer in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Healthcare`, `B) Agriculture`, `C) Tourism`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Healthcare`,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What is the main economic driver for Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Mining`, `B) Manufacturing`, `C) Agriculture`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Mining`,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What is the primary mode of transportation for goods in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Trains`, `B) Buses`, `C) Boats`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Trains`,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What major event attracts international business to Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Brisbane International Film Festival`,
      `B) Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre`,
      `C) Brisbane Festival`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `B) Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre`,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What is the Brisbane Stock Exchange known for?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Real estate investment`,
      `B) Commodities trading`,
      `C) Equity trading`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `C) Equity trading`,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What is Brisbane's main airport?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Brisbane International Airport`,
      `B) Gold Coast Airport`,
      `C) Sydney Airport`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `A) Brisbane International Airport`,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What sector has seen significant growth in Brisbane in recent years?`,
    answers: [`A) Renewable energy`, `B) Manufacturing`, `C) Mining`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Renewable energy`,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What is Brisbane's unemployment rate?`,
    answers: [`A) 2.5%`, `B) 5.4%`, `C) 7.8%`],
    correctAnswer: `B) 5.4%`,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What is the main source of income for Brisbane's local government?`,
    answers: [`A) Property taxes`, `B) Sales taxes`, `C) Income taxes`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Property taxes`,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What is the significance of the Brisbane River to the local economy?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Recreational activities`,
      `B) Water supply`,
      `C) Transportation of goods`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `C) Transportation of goods`,
  },
];
